{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"ee762a70-a358-44f3-be75-1b58f7aab727"},"exam":{"id":"74b37765-53b1-4e0f-85ae-763b423fef88","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"e9yzvx4u-z9ss-opgg-lwg4-h390rywj4hat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account?","explanation":"IAM (Identity and Access Management) controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account. Security Groups and Access Control Lists are tools within IAM that can help make that control easier to manage. AWS Shield is a separate service that helps protect resources from external attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. Thatâ€™s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false}]},{"id":"464c8f56-20a3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following types of EC2 instances is ideal for workloads that process large data sets in memory?","explanation":"True to its naming, memory optimized instances are specifically for workloads that require more memory than usual to process data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/","title":"Amazon EC2 Instance Types"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb152ac1edfe96da5fe255e395003b0d","text":"Memory Optimized","correct":true},{"id":"2f925ef0b67b13f124d684b4e0ca9682","text":"Accelerated Computing","correct":false},{"id":"94a1a3953054d8ece597f4f69bb343d4","text":"General Purpose","correct":false},{"id":"b26f852f8cf53bd055d76deddcadf155","text":"Compute Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"ea999a66bf3ccfec4616d5be49348665","text":"Storage Optimized","correct":false}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"c3f7fb72-1aba-4b4a-a88d-ab28709130ae","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following services are available 24x7 for all AWS Support Plans?","explanation":"All AWS Support plans provide 24x7 access to customer service, documentation, and support forums. For 24x7 access to Cloud Support Engineers, you will specifically need to get a Business or Enterprise Support plan.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a42a69de8cb0bc12c105962bb2df8561","text":"Support forums","correct":true},{"id":"ba4ffb983499bcebaa93c87030f33728","text":"Cloud Support Engineers","correct":false},{"id":"df710f89ebb9e663bd3d66607a0bf413","text":"AWS documentation","correct":true},{"id":"2273d1167a6212812d95dc8fadbae78e","text":"Customer service","correct":true}]},{"id":"ot1uc3t1-d222-o5zj-vont-qso51339d9ek","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services allows you to run complex analytic queries against petabytes of structured data, using sophisticated query optimization, columnar storage on high-performance local disks, and massively parallel query execution.","explanation":"Redshift allows you to run complex analytic queries against petabytes of structured data, using sophisticated query optimization, columnar storage on high-performance local disks, and massively parallel query execution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/","title":"About Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"594025cae6dfa6b9073dc25de93ddb56","text":"Kinesis","correct":false},{"id":"8d4c0b2cef256d21ab680366c8b1c6bf","text":"EMR","correct":false}]},{"id":"19ddf237-f79d-4d25-b0ae-81419166300b","domain":"security","question":"Enabling Amazon GuardDuty automatically grants this service the permission to analyze which of the following data sources?","explanation":"Amazon GuardDuty monitors the security of your AWS environment by analyzing and processing three data sources, which are VPC Flow Logs, AWS CloudTrail event logs, and DNS logs.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/what-is-guardduty.html","title":"What is GuardDuty?"}],"answers":[{"id":"da9b46af667cf2279d002b955813bb34","text":"AWS CloudTrail logs","correct":true},{"id":"6b7cef11406f2fff58dcc619a2b7e482","text":"Amazon S3 buckets","correct":false},{"id":"a70a14359eb44629c70e41470e05570f","text":"DNS query logs","correct":true},{"id":"8db8c2b0bbd0ff71d1d15bb32f69e3b8","text":"VPC Flow Logs","correct":true}]},{"id":"a87b87a1-e801-e917-756a-a78256b2945c","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Awareness & Training is a Shared Control, since AWS trains AWS employees, but a customer must train their own employees. Datacentre Security is solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of an Application within an EC2 instance, and Identity and Access Management remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"4fde53f82fbc6748a0e6b9b51f615287","text":"Datacentre Security","correct":false},{"id":"e40133007bfa03149696a52e6c45b8d9","text":"EC2 Instance Application Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"027e815b818f136c5892cd32b9f87ddd","text":"Awareness & Training","correct":true}]},{"id":"16rz9iw6-s5av-nrg1-1gja-89cbrnwj8uco","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are storage services?","explanation":"VPC is a Networking service, and RDS is a Database service, leaving S3 and Elastic File System as the storage services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/efs/","title":"About EFS"}],"answers":[{"id":"1dbd7e466350bb810a3ea48be7668773","text":"AWS Elastic File System","correct":true},{"id":"94a6c127c422f3501ac2fd0084ebbd25","text":"AWS VPC","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"6e11595bc7ccdbf672fefaababf72939","text":"AWS RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false}]},{"id":"uqrnb9d8-haf3-bm5v-dcoo-t32fx6qgqhwi","domain":"tech","question":"Your application needs a MySQL database, but you need better performance than you could get running MySQL on EC2. Which of the following AWS services should you consider?","explanation":"Aurora is AWS' managed MySQL database. It delivers up to 5X the performance of a MySQL database running on EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"About Aurora"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"f8d3b65d8479a31ebf67cb18dd0a4641","text":"Neptune","correct":false},{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"cpv9q14j-4nnf-wb3n-urul-qo85pzcs4lot","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following best describes a Resource Group?","explanation":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsconsolehelpdocs/latest/gsg/what-are-resource-groups.html","title":"What Are Resource Groups?"}],"answers":[{"id":"02853c1436655d9187bb9d61a5b2ce70","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that share one or more tags or portions of tags.","correct":false},{"id":"7ff9ffa66bb042afad45110ef6296a1a","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","correct":true},{"id":"85a53afa2201152c277b7a584e2933be","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"dabdc344de93e3ccb3d5245b1f871f94","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false}]},{"id":"dln2owy5-ju7b-em4o-t3bo-ry23tbt3vrfy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes Availability Zones?","explanation":"Availability Zones are distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures. Each Region is made up of one or more AZs. Availability Zones host almost every AWS service, including EC2 instances, S3 buckets, and much more. Some services will maintain copies of your data between Availability Zones, but this is dependent on the individual service (for example, S3 can store data in multiple AZ's, where an EC2 instance is tied to a single AZ). AWS's Content Distribution Network (CDN) is known as CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5c9e81d4612f9e8cb24d82a6015586c5","text":"Distinct locations from within an AWS region that are engineered to be isolated from failures.","correct":true},{"id":"c6c3ae50e5264fd89c1ea0bb3c10e963","text":"Restricted areas designed specifically for the creation of Virtual Private Clouds.","correct":false},{"id":"172cd3aac7dce24131bdafec9988a618","text":"A Content Distribution Network used to deliver content to users","correct":false},{"id":"5b3edf7c62ba2925e93886b2fed63697","text":"Two zones containing compute resources that are designed to automatically maintain synchronized copies of each other's data.","correct":false}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"10c453b6-5a2e-4615-9042-6c6fc00a7724","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authorization\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the Authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authorization is a part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":false},{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":true}]},{"id":"cliqnjyx-pd1z-74c0-p0h5-gl8ufv76fo42","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are valid EC2 pricing options?","explanation":"On-Demand, where you pay for the resources you have used at the end of the billing period, and Reserved, were you commit to paying a certain amount every billing period for a length of time no matter if you used them or not, are the valid EC2 pricing options.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"4cc6684df7b4a92b1dec6fce3264fac8","text":"Global","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false}]},{"id":"2d6841a4-2163-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS, you can stop or terminate instances when not in use. Which of the following concepts describes this capability?","explanation":"Elasticity denotes the ability to increase or reduce the number or capabilities of AWS resources when needed. In this case, stopping or terminating instances means that you are reducing the number of AWS resources used in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"857defc5b4c6f1fef867a03c300bdd29","text":"Loose Coupling","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false},{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false}]},{"id":"8d9bfa67-4685-4ba8-a5a7-d0518daba638","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"075e3cda-4e62-4381-bb3f-0cd061c73bb3","domain":"security","question":"A purchasing department staff member is setup as an AWS user in the companyâ€™s procurement AWS account. At each month-end, the staff member needs access to an application running on EC2 in the companyâ€™s accounts payable AWS account to reconcile reports. Which of the following provides the most secure and operationally efficient way to give the staff member access to the accounts payable application?","explanation":"The staff member should be given the ability to assume a role programmatically with the permissions necessary to run the accounts payable application. Setting up another AWS user for the staff member in the accounts payable account will require the presentation of hard credentials programmatically. Both federation and Lambda will require the use of a role as well, but with the added overhead of maintaining Active Directory or the Lambda function.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_common-scenarios.html","title":"Common Scenarios for Roles: Users, Applications, and Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"e9c43624dba6130e04955aabf167b8b2","text":"Have the user request temporary security credentials for the application by assuming a role","correct":true},{"id":"ecd3e317cda9a34ab820e6d6ff70fcf5","text":"Invoke an AWS Lambda function to run the application in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"926f9b540e5d5ff596976f059a7c9cbf","text":"Create a user for the staff member in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"00383ff55511da79680a3cfdf7bd7a1b","text":"Configure Active Directory integration so that you can federate the staff memberâ€™s access to the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false}]},{"id":"d6a825a0-2fb8-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Where do you go to for viewing your AWS monthly charges?","explanation":"Information about your AWS monthly charges are provided in the Billing and Cost Management Console. Cost Explorer, Budgets, and Monthly Spend by Linked Account View are actually three features within the Billing and Cost Management console; they are not dashboards that display your monthly charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/invoice.html","title":"Viewing Your Monthly Charges"}],"answers":[{"id":"1cc9c00d1383db13dd08ad29b47af362","text":"Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"619ed6d20397878e9706fe9fa7c44579","text":"Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"398d49f50aaa9e03a92dd2d3f2c6a389","text":"Billing and Cost Management","correct":true},{"id":"c11363b7e018c4e9c17fd75fef1e3c58","text":"Monthly Spend by Linked Account View","correct":false}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false},{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true},{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false},{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true},{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true},{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true}]},{"id":"pt61wdfy-tnhp-k8r7-te3l-vczb6trwu4x5","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below statements about Amazon VPC is most accurate?","explanation":"Amazon VPC allows you to build a private, virtual network in the AWS cloud, affords you complete control of network configuration, and offers several layers of security controls.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"About VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"15b3b217cc17fcdf1461509394ea0664","text":"Amazon VPC allows you to build a private, virtual network in the AWS cloud.","correct":false},{"id":"c543f2f72255495cbbc56ce672d12564","text":"Amazon VPC offers several layers of security controls.","correct":false},{"id":"b32bdcf3a762c1d6a2c979ee4fd5e2d8","text":"Amazon VPC affords you complete control of network configuration.","correct":false},{"id":"ca15e10364461b0878a8e25af87638ec","text":"Amazon VPC offers all of these features.","correct":true},{"id":"f861cb51390cd12273087e488f8be68b","text":"Amazon VPC offers none of these features.","correct":false}]},{"id":"qlfvvg3n-igqt-be79-1bph-rx4nrjmqmm25","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below statements are correct in relation to security responsibilities in AWS?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud - the security of components that run the cloud service. The customer is responsible for security IN the cloud -- that is, the security of their AWS resources and data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0369ed76a5e4ccb3887e44fe8a7c8703","text":"AWS is responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"d1f8c47a806feef1c562619b465cb202","text":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"7c5f3942078ece3769cd1bcbde2bdabb","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"a1b79685a2bbdb6743277416ad663c24","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"2srflb2w-gpba-wyok-a3ts-v64r4v1vd57h","domain":"tech","question":"You use containers to host your microservices, and you need to route traffic to those applications using a single load balancer. Which of the following services should you use to accomplish this?","explanation":"This routing can be done only with an Application Load Balancer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/details/#details","title":"About the ALB"}],"answers":[{"id":"7be6a0f173a965818e92c1df46c6626e","text":"AWS CodeDeploy","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":true},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false}]},{"id":"4nktsg9p-4zj3-dwhq-6y42-7tns3wptn2q7","domain":"tech","question":"You need a managed, low-cost relational database for your e-commerce store. Which of the following should you use?","explanation":"RDS is your best option: it's a low-cost, managed database solution. DynamoDB is a non-relational database, and not suitable for this scenario","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"7fe48e833035175294ec48b4086b24e0","text":"AWS ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"58dbd4ac6f5e40d5300757915fa51606","text":"MySQL on EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"rku8juy8-m8eo-xhrd-ap7e-a3nhr9045k2l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below is TRUE when considering subnets in a VPC?","explanation":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other, without needing any other resources or configuration. NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway work in different scenarios to allow your subnet to communicate with the internet and are not required to communicate between subnets","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html","title":"VPCs and Subnets"}],"answers":[{"id":"8ff25f40e9a121e4620e1809190ac599","text":"By default, subnets within a VPC cannot communicate with each other","correct":false},{"id":"bdcce4ddcc3bbe6bca2d1851d91ff3a2","text":"By default, all subnets within a VPC can communicate with each other","correct":true},{"id":"ecfdf4b74c36d8d497f1023a5b24e38f","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if an Internet Gateway is deployed","correct":false},{"id":"b5bcf23beb0bab6ed020ef6e8d9026ef","text":"Subnets within a VPC can only communicate with each other if a NAT Gateway is deployed","correct":false}]},{"id":"w5gffphd-hr0c-k6ie-54pn-4jmfwjc6h2bx","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below are load balancer types that AWS offers?","explanation":"Valid load balancer types on AWS are Classic, Network and Application. Service, Web, Database and are not available types, however one of the valid types can be configured for these purposes.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","title":"Elastic Load Balancing"}],"answers":[{"id":"d35b51b639528d580362ca7042de6a0e","text":"Classic","correct":true},{"id":"c2ba7e785c49050f48da9aacc45c2b85","text":"Service","correct":false},{"id":"c6e190b284633c48e39e55049da3cce8","text":"Web","correct":false},{"id":"eec89088ee408b80387155272b113256","text":"Network","correct":true},{"id":"e498749f3c42246d50b15c81c101d988","text":"Application","correct":true},{"id":"0a52da7a03a6de3beefe54f8c03ad80d","text":"Original","correct":false},{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":false}]},{"id":"fb40110c-2ee1-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can you use to analyze data?","explanation":"Amazon Kinesis is used to analyze data and video streams in real time, and QuickSight is used to analyze visualizations of customer data. So, both are classified as AWS analytics services. By contrast, Amazon Detective analyzes and visualizes security data, and AWS IAM enables the management of access to AWS services and resources securely. So, neither Detective nor IAM are analytics services; they actually fall under the Security, Identity, and Compliance category.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"c52be467fd0472e51b0f2acb2f234421","text":"Amazon QuickSight","correct":true},{"id":"12fc352b40e25021e08572ca0f5d2b11","text":"Amazon Detective","correct":false},{"id":"a86087964fb00f6ae81475d2c8c3c40c","text":"AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)","correct":false},{"id":"1590671ce414a2deba7ba0a04fef39b3","text":"Amazon Kinesis","correct":true}]},{"id":"f81195c4-7959-4925-a41d-e50f901cccad","domain":"tech","question":"Your System Administration team lead wants you to subscribe to the RSS feed to be notified of any interruptions to the EC2 service in the N. California and Ohio Regions. Which of the following will enable you to do that?","explanation":"Service Health Dashboard displays the general status of AWS services, such as EC2, and it enables RSS subscription. The Personal Health Dashboard does provide information about the services you're using, but it does not give you the ability to subscribe to RSS feeds.","links":[{"url":"https://status.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Service Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"5b60dd28958c0d6d59a455cc074e4322","text":"Service Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"cf4db9f312542c8284a6ccdefcd98544","text":"Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"087edf830b5f3b392ebaef37ba8550f7","text":"EC2 Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"8e75b153e61c22a8ea4e14aadc7cb4ee","text":"Systems Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"d54df537-f2ee-46a2-b1f4-2c115bdf2044","domain":"concepts","question":"Using Infrastructure as Code is a related of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Infrastructure as Code is a key implementation of Automation in cloud - using Infrastructure as Code allows to quickly and easily deploy and manage your environment without reliance on humans to complete all the tasks. Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, and it allows you to expand out as needed. Elasticity is the ability to go up and down in resources as needed. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false}]},{"id":"43e53065-cb82-4d76-a75d-8407d8f0d339","domain":"tech","question":"What two things make up a tag?","explanation":"Each tag consists of a key and a value. For each resource, each tag key must be unique, and each tag key can have only one value.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"22c56699c70b96c6c2351fbf86177472","text":"Primary key value","correct":false},{"id":"689202409e48743b914713f96d93947c","text":"Value","correct":true},{"id":"897356954c2cd3d41b221e3f24f99bba","text":"Key","correct":true},{"id":"b5e6800855208fbd66985d5f570ffd70","text":"Encryption String","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false}]},{"id":"cd73d505-c09a-44cb-a7fa-0ac6be0f5c99","domain":"tech","question":"Upon attempting to create an additional S3 bucket, you realize that you have reached your S3 bucket limit in your AWS account. You anticipate creating even more S3 buckets in the future for your photos and documents. Which of the following is the quickest solution?","explanation":"The key word here is 'quickest'. Granted, you can delete the S3 buckets of your choice, and you can try consolidating files into select buckets and deleting the emptied ones. But that could be quite a hassle to do, compared to simply requesting a service limit increase at the AWS Support Center. By default, you can create up to 100 buckets in an AWS account, and that is a limit that AWS does not override without officially requesting for a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"46bca3e00e40780aa04c28899f5bbe6b","text":"Simply create the S3 bucket; AWS will automatically override the bucket limit.","correct":false},{"id":"104e2902668d313ccfbc1bc78457e84d","text":"Delete the S3 buckets that you barely use.","correct":false},{"id":"340d5ba6fcedb315c6adee97b1239f3f","text":"Consolidate files into half of the S3 buckets and delete the empty ones.","correct":false},{"id":"e7b93b6f7bea9c58f27912c7974c74d4","text":"Submit a service limit increase.","correct":true}]},{"id":"yhwuezmk-vte7-c3ty-x612-wvd1qi3aw2us","domain":"tech","question":"Youâ€™ve been tasked with assessing your AWS infrastructure in terms of cost optimization. Which of the following AWS services would help with this task? ","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you with real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"bd02384ebb7e76c74ae044ad5cf295c1","text":" AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"ee58e6973ab1b8a94d5434399ac85129","text":"Cloud Trail","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true},{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false}]},{"id":"g7u8frqb-st05-cduw-gbms-boj1g5a4xb99","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below best describes DynamoDB?","explanation":"DynamoDB is a fast and flexible NoSQL database. NoSQL databases are non-relational, and have a dynamic structure, whereas SQL is relational and has a pre-defined structure. MySQL is a type of SQL database and Mongo is a type of NoSQL database, but neither of these are DynamoDB. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","title":"DynamoDB"}],"answers":[{"id":"30baf17e85e225ed9bb718ded752d263","text":"DynamoDB is a an SQL database","correct":false},{"id":"482666cddcef688e890d4b901ebf8a32","text":"DynamoDB is a MySQL database","correct":false},{"id":"f311f0c1ec783313330a4fd83fbb6200","text":"DynamoDB is a NoSQL database","correct":true},{"id":"bbd2da8aa588d6741d84847621ad4503","text":"DynamoDB is a Mongo database","correct":false}]},{"id":"04uew9ya-7pbn-ugmi-3vzh-1erxijop26v7","domain":"billing","question":"You are an AWS Enterprise customer with questions about billing and your overall AWS account. Which of the following AWS support personnel should you contact?","explanation":"For AWS Enterprise customers, the AWS Concierge is a resource dedicated to answering billing and account questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/features/","title":"AWS Support Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"aebccaafe1827e1ed91b1d9a27dac4a8","text":"AWS Technical Account Manager","correct":false},{"id":"bac90b5cd782c7dc092efa042af32e5c","text":"AWS Concierge","correct":true},{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"0037cad42801741c9acb59d7d7ba9a5f","text":"AWS Billing and Accounts","correct":false}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true}]},{"id":"fd9d7891-1f20-431b-81e8-091169615548","domain":"tech","question":"Your sales operations group would like to perform monthly analyses on large amounts of sales activity. They want to be able to rank the performance of different territories, product categories, and sales channels. They will use visualization tools to generate graphical representations of the data. Which AWS service will provide the best solution for storing the sales data?","explanation":"Amazon Redshift provides the best solution for performing queries based on a predefined set of dimensions. Redshift organizes data for high performance based on user-specified distribution schemes. Amazon ElastiCache provides in-memory performance, but no data organization assistance. Amazon Aurora and Amazon DynamoDB are good solutions, but Redshift's columnar storage gives it the edge.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/?nc2=h_m1","title":"Amazon Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":false},{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"ecafbaed9f41dac736e496a7cd234ce4","text":"Amazon DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"0c9f823e-8368-41f9-a5e5-6dbdb7a5d728","domain":"tech","question":"You are creating an S3 bucket called company-subsite-logos, and you want to give it the exact same settings that your company-logos bucket has. What would be the quickest way of doing so?","explanation":"You can choose to select the company-logos bucket to pop up a screen and take note of all the settings in the screen to use for the company-subsite-logos bucket. However, it is easier to simply Copy settings from an existing bucket when creating a new S3 bucket.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/user-guide/create-bucket.html","title":"How Do I Create an S3 Bucket?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2833d56dbb85269cf9923f871b958148","text":"Select the company-logos bucket to pop up a screen. Write down all the settings in the screen to use for the company-subsite-logos bucket.","correct":false},{"id":"8dcfff9aa976530e7cb39a3561f8e013","text":"Right-click on the company-logos bucket. Write down all the settings in the screen to use for the company-subsite-logos bucket.","correct":false},{"id":"a4a7f2e73dfc3676b384b8e28e1b2447","text":"Create the company-subsite-logos bucket. Then right-click on it, choose the Copy settings from an existing bucket option, and then choose the company-logos bucket to copy its settings.","correct":true},{"id":"b3fc5f32c491e7a2f3414331506cd224","text":"At the Create bucket screen for the company-logos bucket, choose Copy settings from an existing bucket option, and then choose the company-subsite-logos bucket to copy its settings.","correct":false}]},{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false},{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true},{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false}]},{"id":"p591e7kl-wfkp-78wh-zz8y-kf2mmf34gdw1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are steps you should take in securing your AWS account?","explanation":"The Root account should have MFA enabled, due to it's unlimited access to an account. You should always create IAM users for individual users, since the Root account should never be used for actual work. Groups should be used to delegate permissions to the users you create, instead of individual assigning policies to IAM users since it makes administration easier. Assigning policies directly to any user is not a good idea, since it can be hard to figure out who has access to what resources with many users.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM best practice"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_create_for-user.html","title":"IAM using Roles"}],"answers":[{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"bd3cf659e9d378f1808cdb33b54baa84","text":"Assign policies directly to your administrative users","correct":false},{"id":"8ef2b84b0ea8ddc5ae686a44387d63d7","text":"Activate Multi-factor Authentication (MFA) on your root account.","correct":true},{"id":"2e679971f295b42ffb5f0228883437fb","text":"Use groups to delegate access to IAM users.","correct":true}]},{"id":"aosxkeh9-qevj-zztz-qgkg-lo0glwr2ccoh","domain":"billing","question":"By default, when using consolidated billing, which of the below will the master paying account be able to do in the member account?","explanation":"By default, using Consolidated Billing only allows the master account to view the billing information from the member accounts - no access is automatically granted for users in the master account into the member accounts beyond this. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","title":"AWS Consolidated Billing"}],"answers":[{"id":"54e29f93505b20fe2cc8af1cce96a33b","text":"View any data stored","correct":false},{"id":"3dbb078ea9c1eaf843d213ba217af3e8","text":"View billing information","correct":true},{"id":"29f838d6149e7ff36b4692f879dbd0a3","text":"Grant access to member account to other users","correct":false},{"id":"25e6de5387e3157c014e2c6f2b0e810e","text":"Make changes to resources","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"ee56fwac-hgmj-xrxe-1u42-pucfbmasuhh1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is not a compute service?","explanation":"Elastic Block Store is a storage service - all others are compute services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"34bc95906489c2d5c9583e3230cd48b2","text":"Elastic Block Store","correct":true},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true},{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false},{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWSâ€™s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true},{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false},{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false}]},{"id":"bfoxiudd-ep8s-9jah-t2ho-96nct3a3mjfh","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following data archival services is extremely inexpensive, but can have a multi-hour data-retrieval window?","explanation":"Glacier offers extremely inexpensive data archival, but requires a 3-5 hour data-retrieval window for standard retrievals - though this time can be reduced for a price. Other S3 storage tiers, including Infrequent Access (S3-IA) can all be accessed immediately, but some may incur additional fees for accessing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/?nc=sn&loc=3","title":"S3 Storage Classes"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"4340570ba672bfa48cd45e3f026c01d1","text":"S3 - IA","correct":false},{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":true},{"id":"31e831ec49678aed7f467f791d1f8704","text":"S3 - RRS","correct":false},{"id":"e9a5105fa288ef2b71c037e42d665d91","text":"S3 - OneZone-IA","correct":false}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false},{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true},{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false},{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they donâ€™t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true},{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false},{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true},{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false}]},{"id":"3lwo2qi6-7yzt-o86p-u1vg-vxwsbedkzwt0","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the Security Pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?","explanation":"IAM, Detective Controls and Infrastructure Protection are key parts of the Security Pillar of the Well Archtiected Framwork. IAM - ensuring that only authorized and authenticated users are able to access your resources. Detective Controls to identify a potential security threat or incident. Infrastructure Protection covers the control methodologies, such as defense in depth, necessary to meet best practices and organizational or regulatory obligations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/architecture/well-architected/","title":"The Well-Architected FRamework"}],"answers":[{"id":"d5552e0564007d93ff5937a9cb3bc491","text":"Customer Service","correct":false},{"id":"b9237ed805ea2fe23003f7e73fc1f7d4","text":"Detective Controls","correct":true},{"id":"96c4db3cd9b4be5b89474dff6d0fe9b1","text":"Infrastructure protection","correct":true},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"a571cb3f6a39b87e03d60bce4e086f6c","text":"Technical Account Management","correct":false}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false}]}]}}}}
